Single
Yes, so today we are shooting for our 3rd single!
Well, it's been a long time since we've had a single.
It's been a long time since we had a poll on the implementation of the second single.
It's been a long time since I've shot a single.
I'm not a little nervous.
I'm not nervous, but I'm a little concerned about how it's going to be shot.
The set will be a little different from what we've done before.
I'm looking forward to seeing the hair set, too.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, OK.
Yes, OK.
OK, OK.
OK, record.
Yes, OK, yes
Last
That's Rust.
Yes, OK
Yes, OK.
Oh, this is cool.
This is really nice.
The right hand impression is starting to look like one too.
It's cool.
Okay, okay.
Yes, okay.
It's nice.
Nice, nice.
Thank you.
Yes, yes, keep it.
Yes. - Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
Hi. - Hi.
Today we're shooting Asha for the third single.
Thank you very much.
There's Android and then there's Android again.
I have the impression that it's going to change in rather small increments.
It's totally different from Android.
I'm wearing this outfit.
Yes.
This time, it's not a digital version.
It's a proper version.
This is the third single.
This is how it was taken.
I'm wearing a new costume.
Favorite point
We tell each other.
My favorite is these shoes.
They're so cute!
And these shoes, what did you say?
If you fold them, you're taller.
It's better not to say.
Look at the height difference between me and Gyota today.
If I don't tell them, they'll say I'm even taller.
I don't care.
I'm 5'5".
My favorite point is...
My favorite point is this one.
A mole.
No, it's not.
No, it's this stone.
The stone.
I don't usually do this.
That's for sure.
I mean, it's not too eccentric.
It blends in with the chic of this place.
It blends in.
It's an accessory.
I mean, everyone's got rings on them, but...
It blends in.
I'm wearing it with a ring.
It's so stylish.
I like the costumes this time.
I love the decorations.
It's so chic.
I'm sure I'll be able to show you a new side of me.
It's Harajuku for adults!
I have one more cut to do.
Let's go for it.
I'll do my best.
That's all. I'm just being cautious.
It's easy for you to look in.
Go ahead and guess.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
This is too cool.
The angle on the back is cool.
Yes, sir.
Yes, so now...
Actually, we're in the middle of filming.
I'd like to introduce some of the outfits.
This is what I'm wearing this time.
It's like this.
Okay, so...
My favorite point this time
This is my favorite point this time.
A ring? It's not a ring.
It's a ring.It's a ring.
I've seen silver rings and gold rings
I have seen silver rings and gold rings
but this is the first time for me to see such an unusual ring
so I like it a little.
And these slender pants.
I myself tend to wear thicker pants
I used to have a lot of room in my pants.
but the fact that the pants are unusually slim this time is also a nice touch.
It's different from my previous costumes.
This is one of my favorite points.
So I'm still working hard on the photo shoot.
It looks great!
I really liked the feeling here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, just like that, back there.
Yes, yes, yes, like that
Yes, yes
Yes, yes.
Here you go, sir.
Yes, sir.
Yes, you've been photographed.
In no particular order.
I'm here.
We're shooting for the jacket and
We are in the middle of shooting the jacket photo and the artist photo.
Well, yes...
We're shooting for the purple and grape images.
Yes, it's purple and green.
Purple and green!
It's a great combination, isn't it?
Well, I've got this...
I love the hearts here.
This one is my favorite.
Yes, I do.
Oh, no...
And the tie, it's red and black.
Amazing.
I've never worn anything like this before.
So I'll do my best for the rest of the shoot.
Please look forward to the finished product!
Oh, what's this?
This is so cool!
I like it.
At this time, you can't see the movement.
Yes, sir
Take a pin-up shot.
Yes, okay, yes.
Oh, hey.
I'm in the middle of a zusazaze.
The point of the costume is...
The point of the outfit is that it has a hint of pink in it.
Well, we still have a lot of shooting to do, so I'll do my best.
This one is more beautiful.
Yes, yes, OK.
Let's get this up in case she's smiling a little bit.
Okay.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
That balance still happens.
Yes, we're actually in the middle of a photo shoot.
I'd like to talk a little bit about my favorite point of the costumes.
Well, you know, this time, the local section
I think it's a color that not many people have seen before.
I thought it was a color that not many people have seen before.
Brown, light color.
And I think my favorite point is this changeable jacket.
It has an interesting shape.
It's a little bit interesting, with the top hanging down like this.
I can't wait to see them all side by side.
They are all different from each other.
I'd like you to pay attention to the overall subject photo when they are lined up.
Well, I'm off to take pictures.
Here we are.
Oh, Japan, in Japan!
Let's see...
Nigiel.
Yosawaka's eyes.
Chile is very strong.
Chile is a strong country.
I'll let you guess.
Where is this?
Polynesia, okay.
Yes!
Here they come.
Wow, this place is already easy.
Miami.
America.
What's this place?
Texas.
Yay.
The Straits of Columbus.The Straits Through Which Columbus Passed
Cape of Good Hope
Hope Peak. It's this way.
Let's take a shot.
Yeah!
There's a lot of stuff here.
This one.
Mauritania.
Famous for its past.
I've never heard of this country.
Wow!
Yes, so we're in the middle of a photo shoot.
I didn't introduce the costumes.
I'll show you.
Here it is!
Yes, I think it's quite unusual this time.
The jacket itself...
It's pretty common in Harajuku.
Harajuku, or Harajuku costumes...
But you don't see jackets in this color...
It's hard to find a purple jacket like this.
And this time, it's green.
It's not that easy to find.
That's also interesting.
And the necklace is also a new look.
I think it's going to be a different kind of shoot.
I'll do my best for the next group shot.
I'll do my best.
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
Hello everyone, this is Gaymaji Binual.
So, today we finished shooting the Asha jacket shower for the 3rd single
Asha jacket shower shooting has been finished!
Yay!
Thank you very much!
Now, if there are any outfits of the day, etc.
I'd like to get feedback from anyone.
Okay, I'll go with Kataoka-san for the most part.
I knew you'd come.
But it's a color I've never worn before.
All of them. Jun is wearing purple.
That's amazing.
The colors are all a little different, but...
But they all had a sense of unity, even though the colors were a little different from each other.
This set also has an adult-like playful atmosphere.
It has that kind of atmosphere.
Playing cards, chess, and so on.
This time it's a little bit more mature.
I think you'll be able to see that kind of atmosphere.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Wada, what did you think?
The costumes?
Was it the filming?
Well, I think I shot Solo Asha, too.
Solo Asha was more chic than ever.
It's partly because I shot it in a more mature way.
Above all, the whole Asha...
The background was a bit playful.
and the placement of the backgrounds.
It's very interesting, so please check it out!
Yes, this is the first single since the poll on the four holes.
I hope you are all looking forward to it!
That's all for now, the game is on me!
Thank you very much.